<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AHSN 2021 Conference Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AHSN 2021 Conference Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the homepage for the conference. This is a placeholder page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote Speakers</title>
      <link>/keynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/keynotes/</guid>
      <description>Information about keynote speakers will be coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>/conf_program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/conf_program/</guid>
      <description>Program will be posted here closer to the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>/register/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/register/</guid>
      <description>A link to conference registration will be posted here when it is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue and Travel</title>
      <link>/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/venue/</guid>
      <description>The conference is being held at the Wellington Campus of Massey University. The Wellington Campus is located on a small hill at the South end of Wellington’s central Te Aro suburb. The main entrance to the campus is off Wallace Street (confusingly, Wallace Street is a continuation of Taranaki Street). It can also be accessed off Tasman Street or through the Pukeahu National War Memorial Park.
GETTING TO CAMPUS For those conference delegates staying in downtown Wellington, especially in one of the nominated conference hotels, the campus is best reached on foot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Submission</title>
      <link>/abstract-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/abstract-submission/</guid>
      <description>All proposals will be blind reviewed by members of the AHSN Review Panel. If you are interested in presenting at the conference, please submit a 250 word abstract with your name, e-mail address, and affiliation through the AHSN website submission portal at https://ahsn.org.au/abstracts/.
Any other enquires regarding the event should also be addressed to 2021AHSN@gmail.com.
New Dates, New Model, Student Scholarships – important updates!! 3-4 February 2021*
Massey University, Wellington Campus, Aotearoa New Zealand</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you have any questions about the conference please contact the organising committee at 2021AHSN@gmail.com.
Conference Organisers Massey University: Nicholas Holm, Bryce Galloway
Victoria University of Wellington: Meredith Marra, Stephen Skalicky</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>